&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, well,
我们回来讨论这个繁重运动的解决方案。
we're back to talk about the solution to this this-heavy exercise.
希望你的手指不会因为打点而太累
Hopefully your fingers are not too worn out from typing this dot and
.到处绑定。
.bind all over the place.
所以正如“读我”所指出的，我们想要做的是重新定位
So as the read me indicated, what we wanna do is we wanna reorient from
定义车间功能使我们的对象，并定义我们自己的对象。
the define workshop function making our object, and define our own objects.
所以在某种程度上
So in a way,
我们真的只需要复制这里存在的所有这些函数。
we really just need to copy all of these functions that exist down here.
我们需要复制所有它们，并将它们放入Object文字中。
We need to copy all of them, and put them into an object literal.
所以我就开始这么做了。
So I'll just start doing that.
我会说Deep JS=一个对象文字。
I'll say deepJS = an object literal.
然后我将把我所有的函数直接放在这里。
And then I'll just put all of my functions directly in here.
除此之外，我要把所有这些
And in addition to that, I'm going to turn all of these
简明的方法形式，因为我不想做财产分配。
into the concise method form, because I don't wanna do property assignments.
所以给我一点时间，我把这些都装好。
So give me just a moment while I wire all these up.
这里有很多功能，不是吗？
There's a lot of functions here, aren't there?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，所以我们在它们之间需要逗号，所以
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, so we're gonna need commas in between all of them, so
别忘了这一点。
don't forget that.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是类语法的一个很好的部分，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That is one nice part about the class syntax,
不必处处处理逗号。
is not having to deal with the commas everywhere.
我会告诉他们的，这是一个很好的决定。
I will give them that, that was a good decision.
好的，让我们把函数取出来。
All right, so let's take out function.
我只是想用一个替换者来做这件事。
And I'm just gonna do that with a replace.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：把那个放回去。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Put that one back.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：[咳嗽]好的，现在我们需要将属性currentEnrollment
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: [COUGH] Okay, now we need to put the properties currentEnrollment
和学生记录，我们需要把它们放在那里。
and studentRecords, we need to put those on there.
因此我们将有currentEnrollment，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是一个空数组。
So we'll have currentEnrollment, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Is an empty array.
StudentRecords是一个空数组。
And studentRecords is an empty array.
现在我们需要开始把我们所有的这些点都扔到每一个地方。
And now we need to start throwing in all our this dots everywhere.
因此，任何地方，我们引用一个属性，我们在词汇上引用为
So anyplace that we reference a property that we were referencing lexically as
变量，或者当我们引用现在是方法的函数时，
a variable, or when we reference a function that's now a method,
它前面需要一个这个点。
it needs a this dot in front of it.
所以我会一遍又一遍地写很多这些点。
So I'm just gonna write a lot of this dots over and over and over again.
this.currentEnrollment。
this.currentEnrollment.
然后是this.printRecords和this.currentEnrollment。
And then this.printRecords, with this.currentEnrollment.
和this.currentEnrollment。
And this.currentEnrollment.
还有这个.paidStudents.
And this.paidStudents.
还有这个打印。
And this.print.
还有这个提醒一下。
And this.remind.
和this.currentEnrollment。
And this.currentEnrollment.
还有这个学生记录。
And this.studentRecords.
matchId在这里是一个实际的函数，它不需要this点。
matchId is an actual function in here, it doesn't need a this dot.
this.getsStudentFromId。
this.getsStudentFromId.
然后这个点，不是唱片，但是
And then this dot, nope, not records, but
this.sortByNameAsc和this.printRecord。
this.sortByNameAsc and this.printRecord.
这些都不需要这个点，那些都不需要。
And none of those needed this dot, none of those.
这个点和this.getStudentId。
And this dot, and this dot, and this.getStudentId.
和this.currentEnrollment。
And this.currentEnrollment.
有人厌倦了打字和看到所有东西前面的这个点吗？
Anybody tired of typing and seeing this dot in front of everything?
这是一种非常冗长的编码风格。
This is a very verbose style of coding.
[咳嗽]我们需要这个.还没有.
[COUGH] We need this.notYetPaid.
和this.printRecords。
And this.printRecords.
和this.getStudentFromId。
And this.getStudentFromId.
现在，我们需要处理具有需要的方法引用的任何地方
Now we need to take care of any places where we have method references that need
被硬绑住了。
to be hardbound.
所以让我们回到过去
So let's go back through and
查找作为回调传入的任何方法。
find any methods that are getting passed in as callbacks.
这不是一个属于属性的方法，所以这很好。
That's not a method that's a property, so that's fine.
很好，那个很好。
That's fine, that's fine, that one's fine.
那个还好。
That one's okay.
在这里，this.getStudentFromId，这是一个方法。
Here we go, this.getStudentFromId, that's a method.
所以它会失去这个绑定，所以我们需要一个点绑定这个。
So it's gonna lose its this binding, so we need a dot bind this.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：然后这里也是一样的，用sortByName和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then same thing here, sorting with the sortByName and
然后用printRecord打印。
then printing with printRecord.
那些需要被捆绑。
Those need to be bound.
然后是另一个，NeedToEnroll需要绑定。
And then another one, needToEnroll needs to be bound.
getStudentId需要绑定，
And getStudentId needs to be bound,
并且，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：NotYetPaid需要是
and, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: notYetPaid needs to be
束缚。
bound.
应该就是这样。
And that should be it.
好的，让我们摆脱工厂的功能，
Okay, so let's get rid of that factory function,
因为我们现在已经做得很好了。
cuz we're very much done with that now.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在我们有了这个Deep JS对象，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now that we have this deepJS object,
这些呼叫应该基本相同。
these calls should basically be the same.
因此，如果我们运行这段代码，我们最终仍然会得到相同的打印输出。
So if we were to run this code, we should still end up getting the same printout.
因此，这只是一个实现更改，而不是外部更改。
So this was just an implementation change, not an outside change.
所以让我们试试，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：Running
So let's just try, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Running
在我们的RunJS环境中。
over here in our RunJS environment.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：啊-哦，我犯了一个错误，我打到哪里了？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Uh-oh, I made a mistake, where did I call?
是的，我忘了，不能像那样调用define工作坊，哦。
Yeah, I forgot, can't call defineWorkshop like that, oops.
所以让我回去吧。
So let me go back.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：必须把它拿出来，在那里放一个分号。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Have to take that out and put a semicolon there.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在让我们看看这是否有效。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now let's see if that works.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这就是我们的打印输出。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And there we go, there's our printout.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：关于我们重构这个意识的问题
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So questions on our refactoring to that this aware
编码风格，这种命名空间模式？
style of coding, this namespace pattern?
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：我猜给定对象设计，对象创建模式，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I guess given the kind of object design, object create pattern,
您会实际地期望有名称空间吗
would you pragmatically expect to have namespaced
在你自己的实践中有这么多方法的物体？
objects with this many methods in your own practice?
或者你会试着进一步分解它吗？
Or would you try to break it down further?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，我的意思是，一般来说，如果我要创建一个对象，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, I mean, generally speaking, if I'm gonna create an object,
就像一个命名空间的东西，唯一的原因是我会采用这种方法
like a namespaced kind of a thing, the only reason I'm gonna go that approach
而不是使用模块方法是因为我知道我有两个或三个对象
instead of going the module approach is because I know I have two or three objects
我想通过一个原型链连接起来，让他们彼此合作。
that I want to link through a prototype chain and have them work with each other.
所以我会试着把这些物体适当地分开
So I'm gonna try to have those objects have their properly separated out
行为，而不是有一个巨大的东西与厨房水槽
behaviors rather than having one giant thing with the kitchen sink of
所有东西都在里面。
everything in it.
我将尝试这三个独立的对象，每个对象都做自己的事情
I'm gonna try these three separate objects that each do their own thing and
它们实际上是通过调用上下文组成的。
they virtually compose through that call context.
好吧，好吧，希望这对这个意识编码有一点启发，
Okay, well, that hopefully was a bit enlightening on the this-aware coding,
还有一些你可能会遇到的问题。
and some of the problems that you can run into.
它们不仅具有异步回调和事件处理程序，
They're not just with asynchronous callbacks and event handlers,
即使是那些传递给array.map之类的回调，
even those callbacks that you pass into things like array.map,
你得担心这个装订。
you have to worry about the this binding.
所以你要小心。
So you need to be careful.
我想说，总的来说，我在这里必须做的绑定用法的数量是
I would say on the whole the amount of bind usage that I had to do here was
在我可能会说的边界上，这种风格的编码是没有用处的。
on the borderline to where I would have said, this style of coding is not useful.
把这个点放在所有东西前面肯定是非常冗长的。
It certainly was very verbose to put this dot in front of everything.
我可能更喜欢模块模式
And I probably would have favored the module pattern for
这种特殊的密码，对吗？
this particular kind of code, yes?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：绑定这个的规则是什么？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: What's the rule for binding this?
因为有时它在使用它，有时它不是。
Cuz sometimes it's using it and sometimes it isn't.
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：是的，这实际上是一个好问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, that's actually a good question.
所以有几个地方。
So there's a couple of places.
我很高兴你提起这件事，有几个地方我应该
I'm glad you brought that up, there's a couple of places I should have
回去说，我们真的需要它吗？
gone back and said, do we actually need it?
例如，sortByName，
So for example, the sortByName,
我们不需要它，因为它不会引用前面的这个点。
we don't need it because it doesn't make a reference to a this dot in front of it.
所以在这里，这实际上是不必要的，printRecord也是如此。
So here, that was actually unnecessary, and the same thing with printRecord.
这是不必要的，因为我们没有任何这方面的参考。
It was unnecessary there because we don't have any this references in it.
所以按照顺序，你问题的答案是，
So in order words, the answer to your question is,
只有当方法是this-aware函数时，才需要绑定它。
you only need to bind this if the method is a this-aware function.
我们在这里有一些关于命名空间的函数，但是
We have a few functions on here that are on the namespace but
没有意识到这一点，所以他们不需要绑定。
are not this-aware, and so they don't need a binding.